[
    {"question": "ويليام", "response": "و ي ل ي ا م"},
    {"question": "نامي", "response": "ن ا م ي"},
    {"question": "لوفي", "response": "ل و ف ي"},
    {"question": "ايرين", "response": "ا ي ر ي ن"},
    {"question": "استا", "response": "ا س ت ا"},
    {"question": "همتارو", "response": "ه م ت ا ر و"},
    {"question": "الويفيا", "response": "ا ل و ي ف ي ا"},
    {"question": "نويل", "response": "ن و ي ل"},
    {"question": "رايلي", "response": "ر ا ي ل ي"},
    {"question": "ال", "response": "ا ل"},
    {"question": "لاو", "response": "ل ا و"},
    {"question": "مادارا", "response": "م ا د ا ر ا"},
    {"question": "يوريتشي", "response": "ي و ر ي ت ش ي"},
    {"question": "ايتاتشي", "response": "ا ي ت ا ت ش ي"},
    {"question": "توبي", "response": "ت و ب ي"},
    {"question": "نوبارا", "response": "ن و ب ا ر ا"},
    {"question": "ليفاي", "response": "ل ي ف ا ي"},
    {"question": "هاشيراما", "response": "ه ا ش ي ر ا م ا"},
    {"question": "بوروتو", "response": "ب و ر و ت و"},
    {"question": "يوسوب", "response": "ي و س و ب"},
    {"question": "ريم", "response": "ر ي م"},
    {"question": "اوتشيها شيسوي", "response": "ا و ت ش ي ه ا ش ي س و ي"},
    {"question": "كيد", "response": "ك ي د"},
    {"question": "ميكاسا", "response": "م ي ك ا س ا"},
    {"question": "دانزو", "response": "د ا ن ز و"},
    {"question": "وينغ", "response": "و ي ن غ"},
    {"question": "تينشيهان", "response": "ت ي ن ش ي ه ا ن"},
    {"question": "بيكوهان", "response": "ب ي ك و ه ا ن"},
    {"question": "كازيكاجي", "response": "ك ا ز ي ك ا ج ي"},
    {"question": "جيرايا", "response": "ج ي ر ا ي ا"},
    {"question": "كازيكاجي", "response": "ك ا ز ي ك ا ج ي"},
    {"question": "كوكومي", "response": "ك و ك و م ي"},
    {"question": "غيو", "response": "غ ي و"},
    {"question": "تشيو", "response": "ت ش ي و"},
    {"question": "ساسوري", "response": "س ا س و ر ي"},
    {"question": "نيزوكو", "response": "ن ي ز و ك و"},
    {"question": "ميدوريا", "response": "م ي د و ر ي ا"},
    {"question": "نيجي", "response": "ن ي ج ي"},
    {"question": "ليزا", "response": "ل ي ز ا"},
    {"question": "كاغويا", "response": "ك ا غ و ي ا"},
    {"question": "هينا", "response": "ه ي ن ا"},
    {"question": "الوكا", "response": "ا ل و ك ا"},
    {"question": "هيناتا", "response": "ه ي ن ا ت ا"},
    {"question": "زينتسو", "response": "ز ي ن ت س و"},
    {"question": "رينغوكو", "response": "ر ي ن غ و ك و"},
    {"question": "كورتا", "response": "ك و ر ت ا"},
    {"question": "هيسوكا", "response": "ه ي س و ك ا"},
    {"question": "انوس", "response": "ا ن و س"},
    {"question": "بياكوغان", "response": "ب ي ا ك و غ ا ن"},
    {"question": "شوكو", "response": "ش و ك و"},
    {"question": "ديكو", "response": "د ي ك و"},
    {"question": "يامي", "response": "ي ا م ي"},
    {"question": "فانجانس", "response": "ف ا ن ج ا ن س"},
    {"question": "يوليوس", "response": "ي و ل ي و س"},
    {"question": "تسوموغو", "response": "ت س و م و غ و"},
    {"question": "نانامي", "response": "ن ا ن ا م ي"},
    {"question": "ايزن", "response": "ا ي ز ن"},
    {"question": "زاراكي", "response": "ز ا ر ا ك ي"},
    {"question": "اوراهارا", "response": "ا و ر ا ه ا ر ا"},
    {"question": "اينوي", "response": "ا ي ن و ي"},
    {"question": "غوهان", "response": "غ و ه ا ن"},
    {"question": "كيريلين", "response": "ك ي ر ي ل ي ن"},
    {"question": "هيناتسورو", "response": "ه ي ن ا ت س و ر و"},
    {"question": "ريتشيل", "response": "ر ي ت ش ي ل"},
    {"question": "لوفي", "response": "ل و ف ي"},
    {"question": "ناروتو", "response": "ن ا ر و ت و"},
    {"question": "سابو", "response": "س ا ب و"},
    {"question": "ايس", "response": "ا ي س"},
    {"question": "رايلي", "response": "ر ا ي ل ي"},
    {"question": "جيرايا", "response": "ج ي ر ا ي ا"},
    {"question": "ايتاتشي", "response": "ا ي ت ا ت ش ي"},
    {"question": "ساسكي", "response": "س ا س ك ي"},
    {"question": "شيسوي", "response": "ش ي س و ي"},
    {"question": "يوهان", "response": "ي و ه ا ن"},
    {"question": "غوهان", "response": "غ و ه ا ن"},
    {"question": "آيزن", "response": "آ ي ز ن"},
    {"question": "فايوليت", "response": "ف ا ي و ل ي ت"},
    {"question": "هانكوك", "response": "ه ا ن ك و ك"},
    {"question": "روبين", "response": "ر و ب ي ن"},
    {"question": "كاكاشي", "response": "ك ا ك ا ش ي"},
    {"question": "ريومو", "response": "ر ي و م و"},
    {"question": "ريمورو", "response": "ر ي م و ر و"},
    {"question": "غوكو", "response": "غ و ك و"},
    {"question": "غوغو", "response": "غ و غ و"},
    {"question": "كيلوا", "response": "ك ي ل و ا"},
    {"question": "غون", "response": "غ و ن"},
    {"question": "كورابيكا", "response": "ك و ر ا ب ي ك ا"},
    {"question": "يوسكي", "response": "ي و س ك ي"},
    {"question": "ايشيدا", "response": "ا ي ش ي د ا"},
    {"question": "ايتيشغو", "response": "ا ي ت ي ش غ و"},
    {"question": "ميناتو", "response": "م ي ن ا ت و"},
    {"question": "رينجي", "response": "ر ي ن ج ي"},
    {"question": "جيمبي", "response": "ج ي م ب ي"},
    {"question": "انوس", "response": "ا ن و س"},
    {"question": "سايتاما", "response": "س ا ي ت ا م ا"},
    {"question": "نيزيكو", "response": "ن ي ز ي ك و"},
    {"question": "اوراهارا", "response": "ا و ر ا ه ا ر ا"},
    {"question": "تانجيرو", "response": "ت ا ن ج ي ر و"},
    {"question": "نويل", "response": "ن و ي ل"},
    {"question": "يونو", "response": "ي و ن و"},
    {"question": "لايت", "response": "ل ا ي ت"},
    {"question": "إدوارد إلريك", "response": "إ د و ا ر د إ ل ر ي ك"},
    {"question": "ألّوكارد", "response": "أ لّ و ك ا ر د"},
    {"question": "ليفاي أكرمان", "response": "ل ي ف ا ي أ ك ر م ا ن"},
    {"question": "زورو", "response": "ز و ر و"},
    {"question": "سانجي", "response": "س ا ن ج ي"},
    {"question": "شينوبو", "response": "ش ي ن و ب و"},
    {"question": "ميدوريا", "response": "م ي د و ر ي ا"},
    {"question": "باكوغو", "response": "ب ا ك و غ و"},
    {"question": "شوتو", "response": "ش و ت و"},
    {"question": "أول مايت", "response": "أ و ل م ا ي ت"},
    {"question": "سورا", "response": "س و ر ا"},
    {"question": "نانامي", "response": "ن ا ن ا م ي"},
    {"question": "كونان", "response": "ك و ن ا ن"},
    {"question": "كودو", "response": "ك و د و"},
    {"question": "ميوكي كودو", "response": "م ي و ك ي ك و د و"},
    {"question": "اسكانور", "response": "ا س ك ا ن و ر"},
    {"question": "غيومي", "response": "غ ي و م ي"},
    {"question": "ماكوتو", "response": "م ا ك و ت و"},
    {"question": "ناتسو", "response": "ن ا ت س و"},
    {"question": "شوبو", "response": "ش و ب و"},
    {"question": "ميدوريما", "response": "م ي د و ر ي م ا"},
    {"question": "ميتسوري", "response": "م ي ت س و ر ي"},
    {"question": "سانيمي", "response": "س ا ن ي م ي"},
    {"question": "هيبارا", "response": "ه ي ب ا ر ا"},
    {"question": "ساسوري", "response": "س ا س و ر ي"},
    {"question": "باين", "response": "ب ا ي ن"},
    {"question": "هيدان", "response": "ه ي د ا ن"},
    {"question": "كينجاكو", "response": "ك ي ن ج ا ك و"},
    {"question": "كروكودايل", "response": "ك ر و ك و د ا ي ل"},
    {"question": "سنبونزاكورا", "response": "س ن ب و ن ز ا ك و ر ا"},
    {"question": "روك لي", "response": "ر و ك ل ي"},
    {"question": "مايت غاي", "response": "م ا ي ت غ ا ي"},
    {"question": "مايت داي", "response": "م ا ي ت د ا ي"},
    {"question": "غيتو", "response": "غ ي ت و"},
    {"question": "غوجو", "response": "غ و ج و"},
    {"question": "فيجيتا", "response": "ف ي ج ي ت ا"},
    {"question": "غوجيتا", "response": "غ و ج ي ت ا"},
    {"question": "غوكو بلاك", "response": "غ و ك و ب ل ا ك"},
    {"question": "اندفار", "response": "ا ن د ف ا ر"},
    {"question": "ميدو عمي", "response": "م ي د و ع م ي"},
    {"question": "رينيس", "response": "ر ي ن ي س"},
    {"question": "رين", "response": "ر ي ن"},
    {"question": "ران", "response": "ر ا ن"},
    {"question": "ريم", "response": "ر ي م"},
    {"question": "ميكو", "response": "م ي ك و"},
    {"question": "اونوهانا", "response": "ا و ن و ه ا ن ا"},
    {"question": "شينجي", "response": "ش ي ن ج ي"},
    {"question": "تشون يون", "response": "ت ش و ن ي و ن"},
    {"question": "سونغ جين وو", "response": "س و ن غ ج ي ن و و"},
    {"question": "جين مو وون", "response": "ج ي ن م و و و ن"},
    {"question": "تشو فيان", "response": "ت ش و ف ي ا ن"},
    {"question": "زاو فان", "response": "ز ا و ف ا ن"},
    {"question": "جاي جو", "response": "ج ا ي ج و"},
    {"question": "دوم كانغ", "response": "د و م ك ا ن غ"},
    {"question": "سوه وونهوي", "response": "س و ه و و ن ه و ي"},
    {"question": "تشون هاجين", "response": "ت ش و ن ه ا ج ي ن"},
    {"question": "بايك", "response": "ب ا ي ك"},
    {"question": "يوني", "response": "ي و ن ي"},
    {"question": "ياسو", "response": "ي ا س و"},
    {"question": "امومو", "response": "ا م و م و"},
    {"question": "ديانا", "response": "د ي ا ن ا"},
    {"question": "جاكس", "response": "ج ا ك س"},
    {"question": "اني", "response": "ا ن ي"},
    {"question": "جين سوهان", "response": "ج ي ن س و ه ا ن"},
    {"question": "لي هيون", "response": "ل ي ه ي و ن"},
    {"question": "ديابلو", "response": "د ي ا ب ل و"},
    {"question": "زورو", "response": "ز و ر و"},
    {"question": "تشوبر", "response": "ت ش و ب ر"},
    {"question": "ياماتو", "response": "ي ا م ا ت و"},
    {"question": "كايدو", "response": "ك ا ي د و"},
    {"question": "فيجابانك", "response": "ف ي ج ا ب ا ن ك"},
    {"question": "دوفي", "response": "د و ف ي"},
    {"question": "ميهوك", "response": "م ي ه و ك"},
    {"question": "سيزر", "response": "س ي ز ر"},
    {"question": "بيروسبيرو", "response": "ب ي ر و س ب ي ر و"},
    {"question": "جاك", "response": "ج ا ك"},
    {"question": "كوين", "response": "ك و ي ن"},
    {"question": "كينغ", "response": "ك ي ن غ"},
    {"question": "جينتوكي", "response": "ج ي ن ت و ك ي"},
    {"question": "ايتشيمارو", "response": "ا ي ت ش ي م ا ر و"},
    {"question": "اورواشيمارو", "response": "ا و ر و ا ش ي م ا ر و"},
    {"question": "ريومين", "response": "ر ي و م ي ن"},
    {"question": "ريوما", "response": "ر ي و م ا"},
    {"question": "موساشي", "response": "م و س ا ش ي"},
    {"question": "ساساكي", "response": "س ا س ا ك ي"},
    {"question": "ادم", "response": "ا د م"},
    {"question": "بوسيدون", "response": "ب و س ي د و ن"},
    {"question": "جاك السفاح", "response": "ج ا ك ا ل س ف ا ح"},
    {"question": "زيوس", "response": "ز ي و س"},
    {"question": "شادو", "response": "ش ا د و"},
    {"question": "نويل", "response": "ن و ي ل"},
    {"question": "فانيسا", "response": "ف ا ن ي س ا"},
    {"question": "اوراهارا", "response": "ا و ر ا ه ا ر ا"}
]
